麦琪:参议员给了我一份工作!
Maggie: The senator offered me a job!
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:媒体关系执行主任.
Maggie: Executive director of Media Relations.
麦琪:我们正在考虑搬到一个叫华盛顿的好地方去.
Maggie: We are thinking about moving to a wonderful place called Washington DC.
克莉丝:美国的犯罪之都吗?
Chrissy: The murder capital of the USA?
本:你们可以去华盛顿,但我不去.
Ben: You guys can go on ahead to Washington, but I'm not going.
麦琪:好吧,各位,我已经决定了.我要接受华盛顿的工作.
Maggie: Ok everyone I have made my decision, I am taking the job in Washington.
杰森:是吗?
Jason: You are?
本:而我会得到一辆车!
Ban: And I'm getting a car!
杰森:是吗?
Jason: You are?
凯特:嗨,我以最快的速度跑过来的.
Kate: Hi, I rushed over as fast as I could.
迈克:我要直奔主题了,凯特,我们来吧.
Mike: I am going to get right to the point, Kate let's do it.
凯特:你说什么?
Kate: Pardon me?
迈克:我们结婚吧.
Mike: Let's get married.
凯特:迈克,我一直等你这句话呢,我太幸福了!
Kate: Mike I have waited so long to hear you say that, I am so happy!
迈克:噢,太好了,那就这么定了.
Mike: Oh, great then it's settled.
凯特:噢,这太意外了.
Kate: Oh this is so unexpected.
迈克:好吧,凯特,我的父母要卖掉房子,搬家去华盛顿.
Mike: Well Kate, with my patents selling the house and moving to Washington DC.
凯特:你父母要搬去华盛顿?
Kate: Your parents are moving to Washington?
迈克:我是说我得为将来打算了.我是说我们的将来,亲爱的.我是说,我们来面对它,凯特,它会有些艰难.
Mike: I mean I have got to start thinking about my future.I mean our future, dearest.I mean let's face it Kate it is going to be though.
凯特:噢,我知道但是我们能应付的.我们可能要节省,存钱...
Kate: Oh I know but we can do it.We might have to scrimp and save....
迈克:有你支持我太高兴了;实际上我在想我必须得找一间新的公寓.
Mike: I am so glad your up for this; I was actually thinking that I was going to have to find myself a new apartment.
凯特:噢,真的吗?
Kate: Oh really?
迈克:噢,是的.但是现在我们可以呆在你那里.
Mike: Oh yeah, but now we can stay at your place.
凯特:我那里?
Kate: My place?
迈克:噢,我们达成一致了!我本来还担心了一小会,我是说我们必须面对我妈妈不在身边没人做饭和打扫的问题.
Mike: Oh then we agree!I was worried there for a second, I mean let's face it my mom is not going to be around to do my cooking and cleaning any more.
凯特:小可怜.但是如果我们结婚了那些事情我就可以做了.
Kate: Poor baby.But if we were married than I could do those things.
迈克:对极了!
Mike: Exactly!
凯特:我会让冰箱满满的,并且帮忙付账单.
Kate: I could keep the refrigerator full and I could help pay those bills.
迈克:啊,凯特,你太了解我了.
Mike: Ah, Kate your reading my mind.
凯特:你可以叫你的朋友过来玩,我可以招待他们.
Kate: You could have your friends over and I could wait on them hand and foot.
迈克:我们真是心有灵犀啊,这真是我们在一起的最佳时间.
Mike: We are so in sync, this is the perfect time for us to be together.
凯特:迈克,你头脑发晕了.
Kate: Mike you are amazing.
迈克:噢,谢谢你,但是我有一整夜的时间来计划这件事.
Mike: Oh well thank you but I did have a whole night to work this out.
凯特:迈克·西沃,我只有三个字要对你说.
Kate: Mike Seaver, I've got three little words for you.
迈克:我爱你?
Mike: I love you?
凯特:养条狗.
Kate: Get a dog.
克莉丝:本,你得帮助我.鲸鱼先生不想搬家.
Chrissy: Ben you've got to help me, Mr.Blowhole doesn't want to move.
本:好吧,那么他为什么不去华盛顿呢?
Ben: Ok, now why won't he go to Washington?
克莉丝:他害怕那没有朋友跟他一起玩.
Chrissy: He is afraid that he won't have any friends to play with.
本:啊,他知道我会去那,还有爸爸妈妈也去吗?
Ben: Well, does he know that I'm going to be there and so will mom and dad?
克莉丝:我说的是朋友,本.你知道他喜欢的类型.
Chrissy: I'm talking friends here Ben, you know his kind.
本:噢,好吧,也许他会喜欢听这个大家伙的叫声.
Ben: Oh, well, maybe he will listen to this big butt thing here.
克莉丝:那是大牛仔花.
Chrissy: That's Bertha Big Jeans.
本:嗯,她应该把花蕊弯过来.
Ben: Man, she needs to cut back on the honey.
克莉丝:你不知道.所有动物都在背后说话.
Chrissy: You don't know a lot, all the animals talk behind your back.
本:你好,鲸鱼先生.
Ben: Hi there Mr.Blowhole.
克莉丝:噢,本,我想起来了,鲸鱼先生和猪爸爸是好朋友.
Chrissy: Oh, Ben one thing, Mr.Blowhole is good friends with Papa Pig.
本:好吧.现在看这儿鲸鱼,你必须跟大家一起搬走.
Ben: Ok.Now see here Blowhole, you have to move with the family.
克莉丝:鲸鱼先生说他生在这里,这是他唯一生活过的地方.
Chrissy: Mr.Blowhole says he was born in this house and it is the only place he ever lived.
本:华盛顿是个生活的好地方.
Ben: Well Washington DC is nice place to live.
克莉丝:本,他被吓着了.
Chrissy: Ben he is scared.
本:别害怕,鲸鱼先生.我们是你的家人.当一家人一起去什么地方的时候,他们没什么好害怕的.是的,是的.
Ben: Don't be scared Mr.Blowhole, we are your family and when a family goes somewhere they have nothing to be afraid of.Yeah, yeah.
克莉丝:什么?鲸鱼先生说他要去.
Chrissy: What?Mr.Blowhole says he will go.
本:耶!
Ben: Yeah!
克莉丝:鲸鱼先生还想给你最深的吻.
Chrissy: And Mr.Blowhole wants to give you the biggest kiss of all.
本:噢,好的.
Ben: Oh, that's all right.
克莉丝:来吧,吻鲸鱼先生.
Chrissy: Come on, kiss Mr.Blowhole.
本:好的.过来,鲸鱼.抬起下巴.
Ben: Ok, come here Blowhole.Pucker up.
迈克:嘿,爸爸.我想我得和你像男人和男人那样谈谈.
Mike: Hey dad, I think it's time we have a guy to guy talk.
杰森:好的.我没意见.但是我现在有点忙.
Jason: Yeah well that would be nice Mike but I am a little busy right now.
迈克:噢,你决定吧,爸爸.可是对于决定未来的事情你能等吗?
Mike: Oh well that's up to you dad, but can you afford to put your future on hold?
杰森:噢,天啊.你一定卖过人寿保险.
Jason: Oh my God, you got a job selling life insurance.
迈克:不,爸爸.事实如此.你知道搬家可能是人一生中最影响最大的经历.
Mike: No dad, it's just that, did you know moving can be one of life's most stressful experiences.
我是说就这样我们就失去了一个可爱的成员,还要听本吃东西.
I mean its right up there with losing a loved one and listening to Ben eat.
杰森:好吧,迈克.你到底是什么意思?
Jason: Ok Mike, what's this all about?
迈克:想听真话?
Mike: The truth?
杰森:是的,20年后,那将是天翻地覆的变化.
Jason: Well yeah, after twenty years, that would be a refreshing change.
迈克:好吧,爸爸,事实是,你和妈妈去了华盛顿后,不知道我会怎么样.
Mike: Ok dad, the truth is, that with you and mom moving to Washington, I don't know what is going to happen to me.
杰森:我不知道你是这么想的.
Jason: I didn't know you felt that way.
迈克:是的,要不是向凯特求了婚,我也不知道.
Mike: Yeah well neither did I until I found myself proposing to Kate.
杰森:你求婚了,迈克?嘿,祝贺你…
Jason: You proposed Mike?Hey congratulations...
迈克:她拒绝了我.我猜这个女人对洗衣做饭过敏.
Mike: She turned me down.I guess the woman is allergic to cooking and cleaning.
杰森:你求婚时提到洗衣做饭了?
Jason: You mentioned cooking and cleaning in a proposal?
迈克:不仅如此,爸爸,
Mike: That's not the only thing I said dad,
我是说我也提及了爱情和租金.
I mean I also covered love and rent.
杰森:噢,你不会为了方便而结婚吧.
Jason: Well you can't get married out of convenience.
迈克:为什么不?
Mike: Why not?
杰森:因为婚姻不是方便,迈克.是牺牲.看看我,我得把我的事业转移到华盛顿去.
Jason: Because marriage is not about convenience Mike, it's about compromise.Look at me, I m moving my practice to Washington.
迈克:你要把你那些病秧子也带去?
Mike: You are moving all your nut-cases to Washington?
杰森:不,华盛顿有的是病秧子.他们也不是病秧子,迈克.噢,嘿,当我最初听说搬家的消息,我说忘了它吧.
Jason: No there are plenty of nut-cases in Washington, and they are not nut-cases Mike.Oh hey, it's just that when I heard about the move, I said forget it.
但是有时感情会让你考虑别人的需要超过你自己,
But the thing about a relationship is that sometimes you have to consider
这时你就会放弃自己的要求.
another person's needs before your own, put yours on hold.
迈克:爸爸,这正是我要凯特做而她有拒绝我的事情.
Mike: Dad, that's exactly what I ask Kate to do and she said no.
杰森:我的意思是说你可以把凯特的需要放在第一位.但是,我们不会搬去华盛顿留下你和一团遭的生活的.
Jason: What I meant was maybe you could put Kate's needs first.But don't let us moving to Washington throw you into a panic Mike.
你要学会照顾自己.你已经长大了.
You're going to be able to fend for yourself.You have grown up.
迈克:我长大了吗?
Mike: I have?
杰森:噢,是的,你该负起责任了,全部…
Jason: Oh yeah, you are ready for responsibility now, total re...
杰森:好的,看,成交了.我给你更多自由;你要向我保证承担更多责任.
Jason: Ok look, here is the deal.I will give you a little more freedom; you've got to promise me a lot more responsibility.
迈克:嘿,没问题,爸爸.我发誓,我已经准备好承担所有责任.
Mike: Hey, no problem dad, I swear, I am ready for total responsibility.
杰森:迈克,我还没有准备好承担所有责任呢.
Jason: Mike, I'm not ready for total responsibility.
杰森:一些责任.
Jason: Some responsibility.
迈克:我听你的,爸爸.我将为自己的生活负责.就从向向凯特道歉开始.真希望我知道该怎么做.
Mike: I hear you dad, I am going to take responsibility for my life.And
I am going to start be apologizing to Kate.I just wish I knew the
right way to do it
杰森:如果你不介意我这么说,我想打动一个女人的心最好的办法就是真诚.
Jason: Well if you don't mind me saying so, I think the best way to a women's heart is sincerity.And if that's not working try a little gift.
迈克:糖果.
Mike: Candy gram.
凯特:迈克,是你吗?
Kate: Mike is that you?
迈克:不,是150磅的棒棒糖.让我出来.
Mike: No, it is a hundred and fifty pound Bon-Bon.Unwrap me.
凯特:走开.
Kate: Pass.
迈克:那么至少看看这卡片.
Mike: Well then at least read the card.
凯特:你要说的我今天早晨都听到了.
Kate: I heard everything you had to say this morning.
迈克:凯特,来吧,这里真热.我都晕倒两次了.给你的.
Mike: Kate, come on, it's hot in here.I blacked out twice already.For you.
凯特:谢谢.
Kate: Thank you.
迈克:我让蜡烛亮起来,却烧着了我的头发.
Mike: I had candles going, but I singed my hair.
凯特:我在炉子上做了东西,请原谅.
Kate: I've got something on the stove, excuse me.
迈克:凯特,看,
Mike: Kate, look I am sorry about this morning.
我对今天早晨的事很抱歉.凯特,
Kate, it's just that with my folks moving to Washington I went temporarily
因为我的家人要去华盛顿,所以我暂时有点抓狂.
insane.
求你嫁给我也只是我的膝盖本能反应.
Asking you to marry me was just a knee jerk reaction.
凯特:你只说对了一半.
Kate: You got it half right.
迈克:凯特,我想说我很自私,幼稚,无知,粗鲁,任性…你该让我停下来了.
Mike: Kate what I am trying to say is I am selfish and immature and thoughtless and rude and spoiled and....stop me any time here.
凯特:当我不同意时我会的.
Kate: I will when I disagree.
迈克:凯特,我真的求你嫁给我.
Mike: Kate, I am asking you to marry me.
凯特:又一次?
Kate: Again?
迈克:是的,在时机合适的时候.
Mike: Yes, when the time is right.
凯特:什么?
Kate: Huh?
迈克:首先,我要完成学业,找份工作,这样才能给你想要的生活.那么你会嫁给我吗,有一天?
Mike: Well first, I want to finish school and start a career, so that I can give you the life that you deserve.So will you marry me, someday?
凯特:也许吧,那一天再问我.
Kate: Maybe, ask me someday.
迈克:嘿,小心点,你会弄坏我糊的花生的.
Mike: Hey, be careful you going to crush my packing peanuts.
迈克:嘿,开萝尔.开萝尔,你在干什么?
Mike: Hey Carol, Carol what are you doing?
开萝尔:随便看看,想想;很快我就要不受这所房子的欢迎了,这种感觉很怪.
Carol: Just looking, thinking; seems so weird to think soon I won't be welcome in
this house
迈克:啊,看起来现在你好像已经习惯了.
Mike: Well, it seems like you should be use to that by now.
对不起,说漏嘴了.
Sorry, it's on auto pilot.
开萝尔:我们从来没有和和气气的时候,不是吗?
Carol: We haven't had the greatest relationship, have we?
迈克:噢,我不知道你怎么会那么说.
Mike: Oh I don't know why you say that.
迈克:哈啰.嘿!嗷!嘿,疼!
Mike: Hello.Hey!Aw!Hey, that hurt!
开萝尔:你好.噢,嗨,
Carol: Hello.Oh, hi Bobby, lucky you caught me,
鲍比,你真幸运能找到我.我正要出门呢.
I was just headed out the door.
迈克:好吧,至少我们不会住在一起,
Mike: Well, at least we won't be living under the same roof,
总是在对方的活力范围之内了.
at each other's throats all the time.
开萝尔:是的.我想这是种解脱,21年后我们也该休息一下了.
Carol: Yeah, I mean what a relief, after twenty-one years together we need a break.
迈克:哇,21年.
Mike: Wow, twenty-one years.
开萝尔:是啊.
Carol: Yeah.
迈克:你总是这么好斗.
Mike: You have always been obnoxious.
杰森:迈克,看看这个.
Jason: Mike, read this line.
迈克:我讨厌这本书.
Mike: I hate this book.
杰森:噢,你怎么知道的?你还没读过呢.
Jason: Oh, how do you know?You haven't even read it.
迈克:我听说过.我要等着看电影.
Mike: I heard about it I'll just wait for the movie.
杰森:迈克.
Jason: Mikey.
迈克:好吧,好吧.别帮我.
Mike: Ok, ok.Don't help me.
开萝尔:(读书)"'看点在跑.'迪克说,'跑啊,跑啊,跑啊.''看他摇的尾巴.'"
Carol: (reading) "See Spot run said Dick.Run, run, run.See him wag his tail."
麦琪:我听见了,她会阅读了.才4岁她就会阅读了..
Maggie: I heard her, she can read.Four years old and she can read
杰森:真是奇迹.
Jason: It's a mericcall.
麦琪:噢,太棒了.
Maggie: Oh, it's fantastic!
杰森:我们的小天才.
Jason: Our little genius.
麦琪:噢,我得去打电话通知爸爸妈妈.
Maggie: Oh, I'm got to go call mom and dad.
杰森:我给她拿纸.
Jason: I'll get the paper for her.
开萝尔:翻页;我想知道结局.
Carol: Turn the page; I want to see how it comes out.
迈克:你总是想让我出洋相,不是吗?
Mike: You have always got me make me look bad don't you?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yeah.
迈克:有你的.那么你能阅读又怎么样,这没有什么意义.
Mike: Big deal, so what if you can read, it doesn't mean nothing.
开萝尔:当然有.这意味着我聪明,而你愚蠢.
Carol: Sure it does, it means I'm smart and your stupid.
迈克:噢,是吗?
Mike: Oh yeah?
开萝尔:是的,你永远也毕不了业.
Carol: Yeah, you're never even going to graduate.
迈克:我跟你独5块钱,我能毕业.
Mike: I bet you fifty bucks I do.
开萝尔:好的,成交.
Carol: Ok, sucker.
迈克:毕业是什么意思?
Mike: What does graduate mean?
迈克:好吧,我毕过业,不是吗?
Mike: Well, I graduated didn't I?
开萝尔:是的,而且你聪明的阻止了我犯一生种最大的错误.
Carol: Yeah, and you were smart enough to stop me from making the biggest mistake of my life.
迈克:你在说什么呢?你还在与德怀特约会呢吧.
Mike: What are you talking about?You're still dating Dwight.
开萝尔:不,我是说我曾经想要做鼻整形工作的时候.
Carol: No, I was talking about the time I wanted to get a nose job.
开萝尔:如果你认为我不知道过去你一直说我长的好笑,
Carol: If you think I'm even aware that you have been calling me funny
你就是疯子.
looking for the past all my life, your crazy.
迈克:开萝尔,你怎么不听我解释呢?
Mike: Carol: why would you even listen to me?
求求你,你知道,你是我妹妹,
Come on, you know, you're my sister and I m suppose to call you ugly.
我就应该说你难看.这是我的职责.
That's my job.
开萝尔:什么,我猜你现在要说你不是那个意思了.
Carol: What, now I suppose your going to say you didn't mean it.
迈克:看,你每次说我难以置信的愚蠢时都是那个意思吗?好吧,好吧,这个例子不合适.
Mike: Look, look did you mean it all those times you call me so incredibly stupid?All right, all right bad example.
但是,开萝尔,拜托,这是兄妹之间的事,
But Carol, come on, this is brother and sister stuff here, you know?
对吗?看,我是说,艾迪说他的妹妹难看,伯纳也认为他的妹妹难看.
Look, I mean Eddie calls his sister ugly, Bonner thinks his sister is ugly
开萝尔:伯纳的妹妹本来就难看.
Carol: Bonner's sister is ugly.
迈克:那不重要,开萝尔.
Mike: That's not the point Carol.
重要的是你不难看,我是说事实上近几年你长的有点,越长越漂亮了.
The point is you're not ugly, I mean as a matter of fact in the last couple of years you're looking kind of, you have been getting better looking.
开萝尔:噢,当然.
Carol: Oh sure.
迈克:开萝尔,这对我很难,对吗?看,
Mike: Carol this is tough for me all right?
我是说,我知道别的男孩子怎么看你,我知道那种表情.
Look, I mean, I have seen the way guys look at you, I know that look.
开萝尔:是吗?
Carol: Yeah?
迈克:是的,我是说,你知道当你的朋友用那种表情看你的妹妹时,那感觉有点怪.
Mike: Yeah, I mean, you know and when your friends look at your sister that way it's kind of weird.
开萝尔:所以你说我难看?
Carol: So you are saying I'm?
迈克:(支支吾吾)
Mike: (mumbles).
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
迈克:漂亮.我说我觉得你很漂亮.
Mike: Pretty.I said I think you are kind of pretty.
开萝尔:哇,你觉得我漂亮.
Carol: Wow, you think I'm pretty.
迈克:是的,看,
Mike: Yeah, look, and if you have any sensitivity at all you will never
如果你有一点明智,你就不要告诉任何人我说过你很漂亮.
ever tell anyone I said you weren't a bow-wow.
迈克:你知道,开萝尔.我一直在想.我是说我们一起相处了21年,你可不能忘恩负义啊.
Mike: You know Carol, I have been thinking, I mean after twenty-one years of my zingers you shouldn't just have to quit cold turkey.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
迈克:我觉得我们给时常见面.以确认你一切正常,不会那么想.
Mike: Well, I think we should get together every once in a while.Just to make sure that you don't start getting the idea that you are normal of anything.
开萝尔:你会那样对我吗?
Carol: You would do that for me?
迈克:当然.
Mike: Sure.
开萝尔:傻瓜.
Carol: Jerk.
迈克:丑八怪.
Mike: Geek.
麦琪:好吧,这是我们最后一顿晚餐.我们就假装这是一次桌椅齐备的丰盛宴会.
Maggie: Ok for our last meal we will pretend that this is an eloquent banquette with a make-believe table.
开萝尔:想象的椅子.
Carol: Make-believe chairs.
杰森:想象的食物.其他人呢?
Jason: And make-believe food.Where are those guys?
开萝尔:开饭了.
Carol: It's about time.
迈克:嘿,披萨.
Mike: Hey, pizza guy.
麦琪:太好了,我快饿死了.
Maggie: Good I'm starving.
克莉丝:噢,好极了,有吃的.
Chrissy: Oh good, food.
开萝尔:真不敢相信我们就要走了.
Carol: I can't believe we are actually leaving.
麦琪:我知道,你相信这是我们在这房子里的最后一餐吗?
Maggie: I know, do you believe that this is the last meal we will ever have in this house?
开萝尔:是的,分享美味的披萨,闻本身上的臭味.
Carol: That's right, sharing stale pizza, smelling Ben.
本:现在把她和房子一起卖掉还来得及吗?
Ben: Is it too late to sell her with the house?
杰森:这房子里养活了四个西沃家的孩子,真神奇.
Jason: It's amazing that this house has survived four Seaver children.
麦琪:我会永远记住这所孩子们成长的房子.
Maggie: I'll remember this as the house my babies grew up in.
杰森:那时他们还只是小孩呢.现在都长大了.
Jason: Well they sure were cute as little kids.And they grow up.
迈克:为什么看我?
Mike: Why are you look at me?
杰森:他是我们听说过的唯一一个能同时在两个城市间留下光辉形象的人.
Jason: Well, he is the only guy we have ever heard of who could pull off scams in two cities at the same time.
还记得你自己到了加利福尼亚,留下本和开萝尔掩护你的事吗?
Remember the time you snuck off to California, you left Ben and Carol to cover for you?
开萝尔:迈克?
Carol: Mike?
迈克:我们养第一条狗时我就在这了.
Mike: I was in here first dog breath.
麦琪:迈克,别给妹妹起外号.
Maggie: Mike, don't call your sister names.
迈克:好吧.
Mike: All right.
开萝尔:妈妈,他整个早晨都在那,还说要一直呆到早餐过后.
Carol: Mom he has been in there all morning and he says he is going to stay in through breakfast.
麦琪:迈克,你不吃早餐吗?
Maggie: Mike, you don't want breakfast?
迈克:今天早餐不吃了,妈妈.
Mike: No breakfast this morning mom.
麦琪:你在这做什么?
Maggie: What are you doing in there?
迈克:不管什么,闻起来很香.
Mike: Whatever it is it sure smells good.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
开萝尔:啊,你知道什么,本;电话准时在7点59响.
Carol: Ah, what do you know Ben; the telephone is ringing at 7:59 exactly.
本:噢.
Ben: Oh.
麦琪:开萝尔?
Maggie: Carol?
开萝尔:知道了.喂.
Carol: I got it.Hello.
迈克:是的,我在丹佛的五个小时真的很愉快.为什么这么小声?
Mike: Yeah, I am really enjoying my five hours here in Denver.Why am I whispering?
开萝尔:迈克的电话!
Carol: Mike telephone!
迈克:我要上楼去接.
Mike: I'll take it upstairs.
麦琪:开萝尔,是谁打来的?
Maggie: Carol, who is on the phone?
开萝尔:迈克.嗯…和伯纳,他在往伯纳家打电话.
Carol: Mike.Umm...and Bonner, he is calling over to Bonner's house.
杰森:等等.迈克?
Jason: Wait a minute.Mike?
迈克:噢,爸爸!
Mike: Oh, dad!
杰森:你哪也不能去.
Jason: You're not going anywhere Mr.'
迈克:我没有啊?
Mike: I'm not?
本:爸爸在和谁讲话?
Ben: Who is dad talking to?
麦琪:迈克.
Maggie: Mike.
本:再见.
Ben: Bye.
杰森:别担心.他不把活干完就别想走.
Jason: Don't worry, he I not taking off until he does his share of the shoveling.
迈克:爸爸,我遇到麻烦了.
Mike: Well dad that is going to be a little tough.
杰森:迈克,5分钟后我在外面等你,别找借口.再见吧,伯纳.
Jason: Mike I want to see you outside in five minutes no excuses.Say goodbye Bonner.
迈克:呃,再见.西沃医生.
Mike: Uh, goodbye Dr.Seaver.
迈克:嘿,看啊.我可不是这家唯一的疯狂艺术家.本尼怎么样,他现在比我还厉害呢.
Mike: Hey look, I am not the only con artist in this house.How about Benny here, he started to get through more that I did.
本:你好,上帝.
Ben: Hello God.
迈克:你干什么呢?
Mike: What are you doing?
本:我刚巧在祈求金钱.
Ben: I happen to be praying for money.
迈克:本,你不能祈求金钱,相信我,我试过了.你以为上帝会给你一张支票什么的?
Mike: Ben you can't pray for money, believe me I have tried.You actually think
God is going to send you a check or something
本:阿门.
Ben: Amen.
女人:为穷人们捐款.
Woman: Money for the needy.
本:谢谢.
Ben: Thanks.
本:来吧,咱们别望了开萝尔.
Ben: Come on, let's not forget about Carol.
开萝尔:我?我一生从来没什么壮举.
Carol: Me?I have never pulled a scam in my life.
麦琪:噢,戏弄波士顿大学的招生老师那次怎么样.
Maggie: Oh, what about the time you tried to fool that recruiter from Boston College.
杰森:还有迈克找来几个无赖装扮成我,去和招生老师打交道.
Jason: And Mike pulled in some bum off the street to play me, in a challenging dual role.
招生老师:真遗憾你妻子不能参加我们今晚的活动.
Recruiter: I'm sorry your wife won't be joining us this evening.
无赖:噢,是的.一想到米奇不能来我就难过.
Bum: Oh yes, I am sick about the fact that Mickey can't be here.
招生老师:不是麦琪吗?
Recruiter: Isn't it Maggie?
无赖:是的,米奇是我们上床时我对她的爱称.
Bum: Yeah, Mickey is just my pet name for her when we are in the sack.
招生老师:好吧,开萝尔,让我说你的高中成绩真是非常的好.
Recruiter: Well Carol, let me begin by saying that your high school grades are nothing short of spectacular.
开萝尔:谢谢.
Carol: Thank you.
迈克:是的,你能相信吗,她得的那些A是在教养院里呆了半年出来以后拿到的?
Mike: Yeah, and can you believe he got those straight A's after missing six whole months because of reform school.
招生老师:教养院?
Recruiter: Reform school?
开萝尔:用刀的一点小误会.
Carol: Little misunderstanding over a knife.
无赖:我们哥几个都以她为荣.
Bum: We are damn proud of the little slut.
开萝尔:好吧,这么个小故事没人受到伤害.
Carol: Ok, so one little scam no one got hurt.
克莉丝:我可从来没做过那种事情,我一直都是个完美的天使.
Chrissy: I have never done stuff like that I have always been a perfect angel.
麦琪:噢,
Maggie: Oh, well what about the time you threw that tantrum because you
上次你因为自己睡了我们却都在玩而扔东西的事情呢?
thought we were all playing around after you went to bed?
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: Yeah?
克莉丝:如果我的记忆力没错的话,我来讲行吗?
Chrissy: Can I help it if I have a health imagination?
克莉丝:这不公平,为什么我必须上床睡觉,而其他人却可以醒着,随便玩.
Chrissy: Its not fair, how come I have to go to bed and everyone else gets to stay up and have fun.
我听见你们的笑声;我知道你们要干什么,等刀克莉丝睡着了,就可以蹦啊,跳啊,开晚会啊.
I hear you laughing; I know what you do, wait around till Chrissy goes to
bed and then party, party, party
杰森:我猜克莉丝一定是困了.
Jason: Well I guess Chrissy must be asleep by now.
麦琪:今晚你想干什么?
Maggie: What do you want to do tonight?
杰森:噢,我不知道.想跳芭比舞?
Jason: Oh, I don't know.Want to play Barbie's?
麦琪:凯特,迈克,我们要跳芭比舞,你们一起来吗?
Maggie: Kate, Mike we are going to play Barbie's, do you want to join us?
莱昂纳多:我要走了.克莉丝睡着了,狂欢开始!
Leonardo: I got to go, Chrissy's asleep and the fun is starting!
麦琪:孩子们,孩子们,如果你们在沙发上跳,就要跳的狠一点,因为弹簧需要锻炼!
Maggie: Boys, boys, if you are going to jump on the sofa you have got to jump harder, the springs need the action!
迈克:你从哪找到的这些?简直太棒了!
Mike: Where did you get these?They are gorgeous!
杰森:圣诞老人送来的!只是等一个特殊的日子.
Jason: Santa Clause brought them!Just waiting for a special occasion.
麦琪:我想玩点别的.我知道有种茶晚会!
Maggie: I want to play something else.I know tea party!
凯特:我想玩化妆的!
Kate: I want to play dress up!
莱昂纳多:噢,跳啊,蹦啊!
Leonardo: Oh, rump rope, jump rope!
杰森:我们有的是时间,我们可以玩通宵.
Jason: We have time for everything, we have all night.
麦琪:谁想吃东西?好的,我去拿些蔬菜来.
Maggie: Who wants cavities?Ok, I brought you some vegetables.
迈克:噢,妈妈,你疯了吗?
Mike: Oh mom, are you crazy?
凯特:不是吃的,是扔的.
Kate: Not for eating, for throwing.
开萝尔:嘿,你们玩又不带克莉丝了吗?
Carol: Hey are you guys playing without Chrissy again?
大家:是的!!
Everyone: Yeah!!
开萝尔:看我拿来了什么!大家都有份!
Carol: Great because look what I brought!Pony rides for everyone!
杰森:我不想破坏气氛,但是去华盛顿的路很远.
Jason: Well I don't mean to break up the fun,
我们最好早点上路.
but we have got a long drive to Washington.Guess we had better hit the road.
迈克:好啊!我也该去见我的新房东了.
Mike: Yeah I have got to go break in my new landlord.
开萝尔:德怀特开车送我回宿舍.
Carol: Dwight is driving me to my dorm.
克莉丝:我们不能等一会看看这些新朋友的样子吗?
Chrissy: Can't we stay and see what the new people look like?
本:我宁愿不知道.
Ben: I'd rather not know.
开萝尔:我也是.
Carol: Me either.
麦琪:噢,来吧,我们该动身了.
开萝尔:再见.
00:21:51,000
Maggie: Oh come on, we had better get moving. Carol: Goodbye.